const Energy = [
	{
		questionText: 'BEE full form & comes under which ministry',
		ans: ['Beauro of Energy Efficency', 'Under M.o.Power'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Energy Conservation Day',
		ans: ['14th Dec by BEE'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Renewable energy day',
		ans: ['August 20'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is the position of India in terms  of renewable energy capacity',
		ans: ['4th'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is the position of India in  Solar capacity',
		ans: ['4th'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is the position of India in  Wind capacity',
		ans: ['4th'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Worlds first solar airport',
		ans: ['Kochi'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Top solar energy producing state',
		ans: ['Raj'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Where is National environment and energy Research Institute',
		ans: ['Nagpur'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'India\'s net 0 target year',
		ans: ['2070'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'India target year to protect 500 GW  energy from Renewable Sources',
		ans: ['2030'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is the share of solar, Wind, Hydroelectric energy in 500GW',
		ans: ['280', '140', '61'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Coal Types',
		ans: ['Antracite', 'Bismite', 'Legnite', 'Peat'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'India\'s position in the Coal production',
		ans: ['4th'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Fly ash is also known as',
		ans: ['Pulvarised fuel Ash'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Petrol is refined by which process',
		ans: ['Fractional distillation'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'By-products in petrol refinery',
		ans: ['Diesel and  LPG'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'LPG contains',
		ans: ['propane and butane'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Examples of anti-knocking agents',
		ans: ['Tetra ethyl lead', 'Methanol', 'Ethanol', 'BTX  Benzene, Toulene, Xylene'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Quality of petrol is measured in',
		ans: ['Octane number'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The quality of diesel is measured in ',
		ans: ['Cetane number'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Gasohol consists of',
		ans: ['Gasoline-90%', 'Ethanol-10%'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is ultra mega power projects',
		ans: ['Which produce more than 4000 megawatt electricity'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Front loading factor(PLF)',
		ans: ['Efficiency of a plant'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which gas is added in LPG to add smelling property',
		ans: ['ethylene Mercepton- sulphur gas '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Gas hydrates is also known as',
		ans: ['Clathrates, methane hydrates'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'In India gas hydrates are found in',
		ans: ['Gulf of Mannar'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Coal Bed Methane is majorly found in',
		ans: ['US'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Coal Bed Methane reserves in India',
		ans: ['Damodar Koyal Valley', 'Son Valley'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which country has highest results of shell gas',
		ans: ['China'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'State has highest reserves of shell gas',
		ans: ['AP'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Extraction techniques used in sale gas extraction',
		ans: ['Hydraulic fracturing-Glaur Gum used in(Cluster bean)', 'Horizontal drilling'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is earth solar constant',
		ans: ['1366 watts/m^2'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'World\'s largest solar plant is at?',
		ans: ['Khawda near Rann of Kuch'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which city in AP selected for Solar City program',
		ans: ['Vijayawada'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who invented windmill',
		ans: ['Anderson'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'World wind day',
		ans: ['June 15'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Largest wind plant in India',
		ans: ['Muppandal Wind Plant-TN'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Largest wind plant in AP',
		ans: ['Anathapuram wind plant'],
	},
	{
		questionText: '',
		ans: [''],
	},

];

export default Energy;
